Easy, boy.
What do you expect?
They're savages.
One lot steals a goat
from another lot,
before you know it
they're ripping each other to pieces.
I've never seen wildlings
do a thing like this.
I never seen a thing like this,
not ever in my life.
How close did you get?
- Close as any man would.
- We should head back to the wall.
Do the dead frighten you?
Our orders were
to track the wildlings.
We tracked them.
They won't trouble us no more.
You don't think
he'll ask us how they died?
Get back on your horse.
Whatever did it to them
could do it to us.
They even killed the children.
It's a good thing we're not children.
You want to run away south, run away.
Of course they will
behead you as a deserter,
if I don't catch you first.
Get back on your horse.
I won't say it again.
Your dead men
seem to have moved camp.
They were here.
See where they went.
What is it?
It's...
-= La Fabrique =-
www.sous-titres.eu
Go on,
father's watching.
And your mother.
Fine work as always.
Well done.
Thank you.
I love the detail that you've managed
to get in these corners.
Quite beautiful.
The stitching...
And which one of you
was a marksman at 10?
Keep practicing, Bran.
Go on.
Don't think too much, Bran.
Relax your bow arm.
Quick, Bran!
Faster.
Lord Stark!
My lady.
A guardsman just rode in
from the hills.
They've captured a deserter
from the Night's Watch.
Get the lads to saddle their horses.
Do you have to?
He swore an oath, Cat.
The law is law, my lady.
Tell Bran he's coming too.
Ned.
10 is too young to see such things.
He won't be a boy forever.
And winter is coming.
White walkers.
I saw the white walkers.
The white walkers, I saw them.
I know I broke my oath.
And I know I'm a deserter.
I should have gone back to the wall
and warned them, but...
I saw what I saw.
I saw the white walkers.
People need to know.
If you can get word to my family...
Tell them I'm no coward.
Tell them I'm sorry.
Forgive me, lord.
In the name of Robert
of the House Baratheon,
- the first of his name...
- Don't look away.
- King of the Andals and the First Men.
- Father will know if you do.
... Lord of the Seven Kingdoms
and protector of the realm,
I, Eddard of the House Stark,
Lord of Winterfell
and warden of the north,
sentence you to die.
You did well.
You understand why I did it?
Jon said he was a deserter.
But do you understand
why I had to kill him?
"Our way is the old way"?
The man who passes the sentence
should swing the sword.
Is it true he saw the white walkers?
The white walkers have been gone
for thousands of years.
So he was lying?
A madman sees what he sees.
What is it?
Mountain lion?
There are no mountain lions
in these woods.
It's a freak!
It's a direwolf.
Tough old beast.
There are no direwolves
south of the wall.
Now there are five.
You want to hold it?
Where will they go?
Their mother's dead.
They don't belong down here.
Better a quick death.
- They won't last without their mother.
- Right. Give it here.
Put away your blade.
I take orders from your father,
not you.
Please, father!
- I'm sorry, Bran.
- Lord Stark?
There are five pups...
One for each of the Stark children.
The direwolf is
the sigil of your house.
They were meant to have them.
You will train them yourselves.
You will feed them yourselves.
And if they die, you will
bury them yourselves.
What about you?
I'm not a Stark.
Get on.
What is it?
The runt of the litter...
That one's yours, Snow.
As your brother,
I feel it's my duty to warn you:
You worry too much.
It's starting to show.
And you never worry about anything.
When we were seven and you jumped
off the cliffs at Casterly Rock,
100-foot drop into the water,
and you were never afraid.
There was nothing to be afraid
of until you told father.
"We're Lannisters.
Lannisters don't act like fools."
- What if Jon Arryn told someone?
- But who would he tell?
- My husband.
- If he told the king,
both our heads would be skewered
on the city gates by now.
Whatever Jon Arryn knew
or didn't know, it died with him.
And Robert will choose a new Hand
of the King, someone to do his job
while he's off fucking boars
and hunting whores...
Or is it the other way around?
And life will go on.
You should be the Hand of the King.
That's an honor I can do without.
Their days are too long,
their lives are too short.
All these years and I still feel like
an outsider when I come here.
You have five northern children.
You're not an outsider.
I wonder if the old gods agree.
It's your gods with all the rules.
I am so sorry, my love.
Tell me.
There was a raven
from King's Landing.
Jon Arryn is dead.
A fever took him.
I know he was like a father to you.
- Your sister, the boy?
- They both have their health,
gods be good.
The raven brought more news...
The king rides for Winterfell...
With the queen
and all the rest of them.
If he's coming this far north...
There's only one thing he's after.
You can always say no, Ned.
We'll need plenty of candles
for Lord Tyrion's chamber.
- I'm told he reads all night.
- I'm told he drinks all night.
How much could he possibly drink?
A man of his... stature?
We've brought up eight barrels
of ale from the cellar.
- Perhaps we'll find out.
- In any case, candles.
Why is your mother so dead set
on us getting pretty for the king?
It's for the queen, I bet.
I hear she's a sleek bit of mink.
I hear the prince
is a right royal prick.
Think of all those southern girls he
gets to stab with his right royal prick.
Go on, Tommy, shear him good.
He's never met a girl
he likes better than his own hair.
Gods, but they grow fast.
I saw the king.
He's got hundreds of people.
How many times
have I told you no climbing?
But he's coming right now,
down our road.
I want you to promise me,
no more climbing.
I promise.
Do you know what?
What?
You always look
at your feet before you lie.
Run and find your father.
Tell him the king is close.
Where's Arya?
Sansa, where's your sister?
What are you doing with that on?
Go on.
Move!
Your Grace.
You've got fat.
Nine years... Why haven't I seen you?
- Where the hell have you been?
- Guarding the north for you.
Winterfell is yours.
- Where's the Imp?
- Will you shut up?
Who have we here?
You must be Robb.
My, you're a pretty one.
Your name is?
Arya.
Show us your muscles.
You'll be a soldier.
That's Jaime Lannister,
the queen's twin brother.
Would you please shut up?
My queen.
Take me to your crypt.
I want to pay my respects.
We've been riding
for a month, my love.
Surely the dead can wait.
Ned.
Where's the Imp?
Where is our brother?
Go and find the little beast.
Tell me about Jon Arryn.
One minute he was fine and then...
Burned right through him,
whatever it was.
I loved that man.
We both did.
He never had to teach you much,
but me?
You remember me at 16?
All I wanted to do
was crack skulls and fuck girls.
- He showed me what was what.
- Aye.
Don't look at me like that.
It's not his fault I didn't listen.
I need you, Ned...
down at King's Landing, not up here
where you're no damn use to anybody.
Lord Eddard Stark,
I would name you
the Hand of the King.
I'm not worthy of the honor.
I'm not trying to honor you.
I'm trying to get you to run my kingdom
while I eat, drink and whore
my way to an early grave.
Damn it, Ned, stand up.
You helped me win the Iron Throne,
now help me keep the damn thing.
We were meant to rule together.
If your sister had lived,
we'd have been bound by blood.
Well, it's not too late.
I have a son, you have a daughter.
We'll join our houses.
It is true what they say
about the northern girls.
Did you hear
the king's in Winterfell?
I did hear something about that.
And the queen and her twin brother.
They say that he is the most handsome
man in the Seven Kingdoms.
And the other brother?
- The queen has two brothers?
- There's the pretty one,
and there's the clever one.
I hear they call him the Imp.
I hear he hates that nickname.
I hear he's more than earned it.
I hear he's a drunken little lecher,
prone to all manner of perversions.
Clever girl.
We've been expecting you,
Lord Tyrion.
Have you?
Already?
The gods gave me one blessing.
- Don't get up.
- My lord.
Should I explain to you the meaning
of a closed door in a whorehouse,
brother?
You have much to teach me, no doubt,
but our sister craves your attention.
She has odd cravings, our sister.
A family trait.
Now the Starks are feasting us
at sundown.
Don't leave me alone
with these people.
I'm sorry, I've begun
the feast a bit early.
And this is the first
of many courses.
I thought you might say that.
But since we're short on time...
Come on, girls.
See you at sundown.
Close the door!
Did you have to bury her
in a place like this?
She should be on a hill somewhere
with the sun
and the clouds above her.
She was my sister.
This is where she belongs.
She belonged with me.
In my dreams, I kill him every night.
It's done, Your Grace.
The Targaryens are gone.
Not all of them.
Daenerys!
Daenerys.
There's our bride-to-be.
Look,
a gift from Illyrio.
Touch it.
Go on, feel the fabric.
Isn't he a gracious host?
We've been his guests for over a year
and he's never asked us for anything.
Illyrio's no fool.
He knows I won't forget my friends
when I come into my throne.
You still slouch.
Let them see.
You have a woman's body now.
I need you to be perfect today.
Can you do that for me?
You don't want to wake
the dragon, do you?
No.
When they write the history
of my reign, sweet sister,
they will say it began today.
It's too hot, my lady.
Where is he?
The Dothraki are not known
for their punctuality.
May I present my honored guests?
Viserys of House Targaryen,
the third of his name,
the rightful King of the Andals
and the First Men,
and his sister
Daenerys of House Targaryen.
Do you see how long his hair is?
When Dothraki are defeated in combat,
they cut off their braids so the whole
world can see their shame.
Khal Drogo has never been defeated.
He's a savage, of course,
but one of the finest killers alive.
And you will be his queen.
Come forward, my dear.
Where is he going?!
- The ceremony is over.
- But he didn't say anything.
Did he like her?
Trust me, Your Grace,
if he didn't like her, we'd know.
It won't be long now.
Soon you will cross the Narrow Sea
and take back your father's throne.
The people drink secret toasts
to your health.
They cry out for their true king.
When will they be married?
Soon.
The Dothraki
never stay still for long.
Is it true they lie
with their horses?
I wouldn't ask Khal Drogo.
Do you take me for a fool?
I take you for a king.
Kings lack the caution of common men.
My apologies if I've given offense.
I know how to play a man like Drogo.
I give him a queen
and he gives me an army.
I don't want to be his queen.
I want to go home.
So do I.
I want us both to go home,
but they took it from us.
So tell me, sweet sister,
how do we go home?
I don't know.
We go home with an army.
With Khal Drogo's army.
I would let
his whole tribe fuck you...
All 40,000 men and their horses too
if that's what it took.
Do you think Joffrey will like me?
What if he thinks I'm ugly?
Then he is the stupidest prince
that ever lived.
He's so handsome.
When would we be married?
Soon? Or do we have to wait?
Hush now.
Your father hasn't even said yes.
Why would he say no?
He'd be the second most powerful man
in the kingdoms.
He'd have to leave home.
He'd have to leave me.
And so would you.
You left your home to come here.
And I'd be queen someday.
Please make father say yes!
- Sansa...
- Please please!
It's the only thing I ever wanted.
Fill that up!
Boys, Rodrik, come on.
Is he dead yet?
Uncle Benjen.
You got bigger.
Rode all day.
Didn't want to leave
you alone with the Lannisters.
Why aren't you at the feast?
Lady Stark thought
it might insult the royal family
to seat a bastard in their midst.
Well, you're always
welcome on the wall.
No bastard was ever refused
a seat there.
So take me with you when you go back.
Father will let me if you ask him.
I know he will.
The wall isn't going anywhere.
I'm ready to swear your oath.
You don't understand
what you'd be giving up.
We have no families.
- None of us will ever father sons...
- I don't care about that!
You might, if you knew what it meant.
I'd better get inside,
rescue your father from his guests.
We'll talk later.
Your uncle's in the Night's Watch.
What are you doing back there?
Preparing for a night
with your family.
I've always wanted to see the Wall.
You're Tyrion Lannister,
- the queen's brother?
- My greatest accomplishment.
And you...
you're Ned Stark's bastard, aren't you?
Did I offend you?
Sorry.
You are the bastard though.
Lord Eddard Stark is my father.
And Lady Stark is not your mother,
making you the bastard.
Let me give you some advice, bastard.
Never forget what you are.
The rest of the world will not.
Wear it like armor
and it can never be used to hurt you.
What the hell do you know
about being a bastard?
All dwarves are bastards
in their father's eyes.
You at a feast...
It's like a bear in a trap.
The boy I beheaded...
- Did you know him?
- Of course I did. Just a lad.
And he was tough, Ned,
a true ranger.
He was talking madness.
Said the walkers
slaughtered his friends.
The two he was with
are still missing.
A wildling ambush.
Maybe.
Direwolves south of the Wall,
talk of the walkers,
and my brother might be
the next Hand of the King.
Winter is coming.
Uncle Benjen.
Robb boy.
- How are you?
- I'm good.
Is this your first time
in the North, Your Grace?
Lovely country.
I'm sure it's very grim
after King's Landing.
I remember how scared I was
when Ned brought me
up here for the first time.
Hello, little dove.
But you are a beauty.
- How old are you?
- 13, Your Grace.
You're tall.
Still growing?
I think so, Your Grace.
And have you bled yet?
No, Your Grace.
Your dress, did you make it?
Such a talent.
You must make something for me.
I hear we might share
a grandchild someday.
I hear the same.
Your daughter will do well
in the Capital.
Such a beauty shouldn't stay
hidden up here forever.
Your pardon.
I hear we might be neighbors soon.
I hope it's true.
The king has honored me
with his offer.
I'm sure we'll have a tournament to
celebrate your new title, if you accept.
It would be good
to have you on the field.
The competition
has become a bit stale.
- I don't fight in tournaments.
- No?
Getting a little old for it?
I don't fight in tournaments
because when I fight a man for real
I don't want him to know
what I can do.
Well said.
Arya!
It's not funny!
She always does this.
This was my favorite dress.
She always does it
and it's not funny!
Time for bed.
I'm a Northman.
I belong here with you,
not down south
in that rats' nest
they call a Capital.
I won't let him take you.
The king takes what he wants.
That's why he's king.
I'll say,
"Listen, fat man."
"You are not taking
my husband anywhere.
"He belongs to me now."
How did he get so fat?
He only stops eating
when it's time for a drink.
It's Maester Luwin, my lord.
Send him in.
Pardon, my lord, my lady.
A rider in the night...
From your sister.
Stay.
This was sent from the Eyrie.
What's she doing at the Eyrie?
She hasn't been back there
since her wedding.
What news?
She's fled the Capital.
She says Jon Arryn was murdered.
By the Lannisters.
She says the king is in danger.
She's fresh widowed, Cat.
She doesn't know what she's saying.
Lysa's head would be
on a spike right now
if the wrong people
had found that letter.
Do you think
she would risk her life...
her son's life...
if she wasn't certain
her husband was murdered?
If this news is true
and the Lannisters
conspire against the Throne,
who but you can protect the king?
They murdered the last Hand.
Now you want Ned to take the job?
The king rode for a month
to ask for Lord Stark's help.
He's the only one he trusts.
You swore the king an oath, my Lord.
He's spent half his life
fighting Robert's wars.
He owes him nothing.
Your father and brother
rode south once
on a king's demand.
A different time.
A different king.
When do I meet with the Khal?
We need to begin planning the invasion.
If Khal Drogo
has promised you a crown,
- you shall have it.
- When?
When their omens favor war.
I piss on Dothraki omens.
I've waited 17 years
to get my throne back.
A Dothraki wedding
without at least three deaths
is considered a dull affair.
A small gift, for the new Khaleesi...
Songs and Histories
from the Seven Kingdoms.
Thank you, Ser.
Are you from my country?
Ser Jorah Mormont of Bear Island.
I served your father for many years.
Gods be good, I hope to always
serve the rightful king.
Dragon's eggs, Daenerys,
from the Shadow Lands beyond Asshai.
The ages have turned them to stone,
but they will always be beautiful.
Thank you, magister.
She's beautiful.
Ser Jorah, I don't know how to say
thank you in Dothraki.
There is no word
for thank you in Dothraki.
Make him happy.
No.
Do you know the common tongue?
Is "no" the only word that you know?
No.
Rough night, Imp?
If I get through this
without squirting
from one end or the other
it'll be a miracle.
I didn't pick you for a hunter.
The greatest in the land...
my spear never misses.
It's not hunting if you pay for it.
Are you as good with a spear
as you used to be?
No, but I'm still better than you.
I know what I'm putting you through.
Thank you for saying yes.
I only ask you because I need you.
You're a loyal friend.
You hear me?
A loyal friend.
The last one I've got.
- I hope I'll serve you well.
- You will.
And I'll make sure you don't look
so fucking grim all the time.
Come on, boys,
let's go kill some boar!
Come on, you.
Are you completely mad?
- He saw us.
- It's all right, it's all right.
He saw us!
I heard you the first time.
Quite the little climber, aren't you?
- How old are you, boy?
- 10.
10.
The things I do for love.