-= La Fabrique =-
www.sous-titres.eu
Summoned to court to answer
for the crimes of your bannermen
Gregor Clegane, the Mountain.
Arrive within the fortnight
or be branded an enemy of the crown.
Poor Ned Stark.
Brave man, terrible judgment.
Attacking him was stupid.
Lannisters...
don't act like fools.
Are you gonna say something clever?
Go on. Say something clever.
Catelyn Stark took my brother.
- Why is he still alive?
- Tyrion?
Ned Stark.
One of our men interfered.
He speared him through the leg
before I could finish him.
Why is he still alive?
- It wouldn't have been clean.
- "Clean"!
You spend to much time worrying
about what other people think of you.
I could care less
what anyone thinks of me.
That's what you want people
to think of you.
It's the truth.
When you hear them whispering
Kingslayer behind your back,
doesn't it bother you?
Of course, it bothers me.
The lion doesn't concern himself
with the opinions of a sheep.
I suppose I should be grateful
that your vanity go in the way
of your recklessness.
I'm giving you half of our forces.
30 000 men.
You will bring them
to Catelyn Stark's girlhood home
and remind her that Lannisters
pay their debts.
I didn't realize you place
such a high value on my brother's life.
He's a Lannister.
He might be the lowest
of the Lannisters, but he's one of us.
And every day
that he remains a prisoner,
the less our name commands respect.
So the lion does concern himself
with the opinion...
It's not an opinion, it's a fact.
If another house
can seize one of our own,
and hold him captive, with impunity,
we are no longer
a house to be feared.
Your mother's dead.
Before long I'll be dead.
And you, and your brother,
and your sister
and all of her children,
all of us dead,
all of us rotting in the ground,
It's the family name that lives on.
It's all that lives on.
Not your personal glory,
not your honor, but family.
Do you understand?
You're blessed with abilities
that few men possess.
You're blessed to belong to the most
powerful family in the kingdoms.
And you're still blessed with youth.
And what have you done
with these blessings?
You served as a glorified bodyguard
for two kings.
One a mad man.
The other a drunk.
The future of our family will be
determined in these next few months.
We could establish a dynasty
that would last a thousand years.
Or we could collapse into nothing.
As the Targaryens did.
I need you to become the man
you were always meant to be.
Not next year. Not tomorrow.
Now!
You're in pain.
I've had worse, My Lady.
Perhaps it's time to go home.
The south
doesn't seem to agree with you.
I know the truth Jon Arryn died for.
Do you, Lord Stark?
Is that why you called me here,
to pose me riddles?
Has he done this before?
Jaime would have killed him.
My brother is worth
a thousand of your friend.
Your brother?
Or your lover?
The Targaryens wed brothers and sisters
for three hundred years,
to keep the bloodlines pure.
Jaime and I are more
than brother and sister.
We shared a womb.
We came into this world together.
We belong together.
My son saw you with him.
Do you love your children?
- With all my heart.
- No more that I love mine.
- And they're all Jaime's.
- Thank the Gods.
When Robert leaves his whores
to stumble drunk into my bed,
I finish him off in other ways.
- In the morning, he doesn't remember.
- You've always hated him.
Hated him?
I worshiped him.
Every girl in the Seven's Kingdom
dreamed of him,
but he was mine by oath.
And when I finally saw him
on our wedding day
in the Sept of Baelor,
lean and fierce and black-bearded,
it was the happiest moment of my life.
That night, he crawled on top of me,
stinking of wine
and did what he did...
what little he could do.
And whispered in my ear "Lyanna".
Your sister was a corpse
and I was a living girl
and he loved her more than me.
When the King returns from his hunts,
I'll tell him the truth.
You must be gone by then.
You and your children.
I will not have
their blood on my hands.
Go as far away as you can.
With as many men as you can.
Because wherever you go...
Robert's wrath will follow you.
And what of my wrath, Lord Stark?
You should have taken
the realm for yourself.
Jaime told me
about the day King's Landing fell.
He was sitting in the Iron Throne,
and you made him give it up.
All you needed to do
was climb those steps yourself.
Such a sad mistake.
I've made many mistakes in my life.
But that wasn't one of them.
Oh, but it was.
When you play the game of thrones,
you win or you die.
There is no middle ground.
Is that what they teach you
up in the North?
And you, wherever you're from,
do you have any idea
how ridiculous you sound?
Either of you understand
a thing that I'm saying?
Yes, my Lord.
Let's start over, shall we?
You be the man,
and you be the woman.
Well, go ahead!
Slowly.
You're not fooling them.
They just paid you,
they know what you are.
They know it's all just an act.
Your job is to make them forget
what they know.
That takes time.
You need to...
ease into it.
Go ahead.
Ease into it.
He's winning you over
in spite of yourself.
You're starting to like this.
He wants to believe you.
He's enjoyed his cock,
why shouldn't you?
He knows he's better than other men.
He's always known it deep down inside,
now he has proof.
He's so good,
he's reaching something deep inside
of you that no one even knew was there.
Overcoming your very nature.
Why don't you join us, my Lord?
I'm saving myself for another.
What she doesn't know won't hurt her.
A stupid saying.
What we don't know
is usually what gets us killed.
She must be very beautiful.
Not really.
Impeccable bloodlines, though.
- I do believe my Lord's in love.
- For many years.
Most of my life, really.
Play with her ass.
And she loved me too.
I was her little confidant.
Her plaything.
She could tell me anything at all.
She told me about all
the horses that she liked.
The castle she wanted to live in.
The man that she wanted to marry.
A Northerner,
with a jaw like an anvil.
So I challenged him to a duel, I mean,
why not, I'd read all the stories.
The little hero always beats
the big villain in all the stories.
In the end,
she wouldn't even let him kill me.
"He's just a boy",
she said.
"Please don't hurt him."
So, he gave me a nice little scar
to remember him by and off they went.
Is she still married to him?
He got himself killed
before the wedding.
And she ended up with his brother,
an even more impressive specimen.
She loves him, I'm afraid.
And why wouldn't she?
Who could compare to him?
He's just so...
good.
Do you know what I learned,
losing that duel?
I learned that I'll never win,
not that way.
That's their game.
Their rules.
I'm not going to fight them.
I'm going to fuck them.
That's what I know.
That's what I am.
And only by admitting what we are
can we get what we want.
And what do you want?
Everything, my dear.
Everything there is.
Now wash yourselves,
both of you are working tonight.
You are a very lucky girl,
do you know that?
Where I come from,
we don't show mercy to criminals.
Where I come from, if someone
like you attacked a little Lord,
at low tide we'd lay you
on your back, on the beach,
your hands and feet
chained to four stakes.
Sea would come in closer and closer.
You'd see death creeping towards you
a few inches at a time.
Where is it you come from?
The Iron Islands.
Are they far away?
Never heard of the Iron Islands?
Trust me...
you've never heard
where I'm from neither.
Trust me, my Lord.
You're not in the wilderness anymore.
In civilized lands, you refer
to your betters by their proper titles.
And what's that?
Lord.
Why?
What do you mean, why?
My father is Balon Greyjoy,
Lord of the Iron Islands.
What's that got to do with you?
If your father's Lord,
how can you be Lord too?
I will be Lord after my father...
- So you're not Lord now.
- No, you...
You're having a go at me?
Is that it?
Just don't understand
how you southerners do things.
I'm not a southerner.
You're from south of the Wall.
That makes you a southerner to me.
You are an impudent little wench,
aren't you?
Couldn't say, my Lord.
I don't know what "impunent" means.
Impudent.
It means rude,
Disrespectful.
Do you want to lose that chain?
Theon Greyjoy!
The lady is our guest.
I thought she was our prisoner.
Are the two mutually exclusive
in your experience?
Chances are I won't be nearby
the next time that happens.
I'm used to worse than him.
I'm used to men
who could chew that boy up,
and pick their teeth with his bones.
Why did you come here?
Didn't mean to come here.
Meant to get
much further south than this.
As far south, as south goes.
Before the long night comes.
Why?
What are you afraid of?
There are things that sleep in the day
and hunt at night.
- Owls and shadow-cats.
- I'm not talking about that.
The things you speak of.
They've been gone
for thousands of years.
They wasn't gone, old man.
They was sleeping.
And they ain't sleeping no more.
I miss girls.
Not even talking to them.
I never talk to them.
Just looking at them.
Hearing them giggle.
Don't you miss girls?
Riders!
The horn.
We have to blow the horn.
Why is he alone?
One blast for a ranger returning.
Two for wildlings.
- Three for...
- There's no rider.
That's my uncle Benjen's horse?
Where's my uncle?
It's Robert.
We were hunting. A boar.
I should have spent
more time with you.
Shown you how to be a man.
I was never meant to be a father.
Go on.
You don't want to see this.
My fault.
Too much wine.
Missed my thrust.
It stinks.
It Stinks like death.
Don't think I can't smell it.
I paid the bastard back, Ned.
I drove my knife
right through his brain.
You ask them if I didn't. Ask them!
I want the funeral feast to be
the biggest the kingdom ever saw.
And I want everyone to taste
the boar that caught me.
Now Leave us, the lot of you,
I need to talk to Ned.
- Robert, my sweet...
- Out, all of you.
You damned fool.
Paper and ink on the table.
Write down what I say.
In the name of Robert,
of the house Baratheon,
First of...
you know how it goes,
fill in the damn titles,
I hereby command
Eddard
of House Stark, titles, titles...
to serve as a Lord Regent
and Protector of the Realm
upon my death,
to rule in my stead
until my son Joffrey comes of age.
Give it over.
Give it to the council.
After I'm dead.
At least,
they'll say I did this right.
This one thing.
You'll rule now.
You'll hate it worse than I did.
But you'll do it well.
The girl.
Daenerys.
You were right.
Varys, Littlefinger,
my brother, worthless.
No one to tell me no, but you.
Only you.
Let her live.
Stop it, if it's not too late.
I will.
My son...
help him, Ned.
Make him better than me.
I'll do everything I can
to honor your memory.
My memory?
King Robert Baratheon,
murdered by a pig.
Give me something for the pain,
and let me die.
Give him milk of the poppy.
He was reeling from the wine.
He commanded us to...
step aside, but...
I failed him.
No man could have protected him
from himself.
I wonder, Ser Barristan,
who gave the King this wine?
His squire.
From the King's own skin.
His squire? The Lannister boy?
Such a dutiful boy, to make sure
His Grace did not lack
of refreshment.
I do hope the poor lad
does not blame himself.
His Grace has had a change of heart
concerning Daenerys Targaryen.
Whatever arrangements you made,
unmake them, at once.
I'm afraid those birds have flown.
The girl is likely dead already.
My...
throne.
Throne.
Can you help me make him understand?
The Dothrakis do things
in their own time for their own reasons.
Have patience, Khaleesi.
We will go home, I promise you.
My brother was a fool,
I know, but he was
the rightful heir to the Seven Kingdoms.
- Have I said something funny, sir?
- Forgive me, Khaleesi,
but your ancestor, Aegon the Conqueror,
didn't seize six of the Kingdoms
because they were his right,
he had no right to them,
He seized them because he could.
And because he had dragons.
Having a few dragons
makes things easier.
- You don't believe it.
- Have you ever seen a dragon, Khaleesi?
I believe
what my eyes and ears report.
As for the rest, it was 300 years ago,
who knows what really happened?
Now if you'll pardon me,
I'll seek out the merchant captain,
see if he has any letters for me.
- Well, I come with you.
- No, no, don't trouble yourself.
Enjoy the market.
I'll rejoin you soon enough.
Jorah, the Andal.
The Spider sends his greetings,
and his congratulations.
A royal pardon.
You can go home, now.
My son already has his name,
but I'll try your summerwine.
Just a taste.
My Lady, you are from Westeros?
You have the honor of addressing
Daenerys of the House Targaryen.
Khaleesi of the riding men
and princess of the Seven Kingdoms.
- Princess.
- Rise.
- I'd still like to taste that wine.
- That?
Dornish swill,
not worthy of a princess.
I have a dry red, from the Arbor.
Nectar of the Gods.
Let me give you a cask.
- A gift.
- You honor me, Ser.
The honor is all mine.
You know there are many in your homeland
that pray for your return, princess.
I hope to repay
your kindness someday.
- Something wrong?
- I have a thirst. Open it.
The wine is for the Khaleesi,
it's not for you.
Open it.
Pour.
It would be a crime to drink it
without giving it time to breathe.
Do as he says.
As the princess commands.
Sweet, isn't it?
Can you smell the fruit, Ser?
Taste it.
Tell me that that is not the finest wine
that has ever touched your tongue.
You first.
I'm afraid I am not worthy
of the vintage.
Beside it is a poor wine merchant
who would drink up his own wares.
You will drink.
Come.
You came to us as outlaws,
poachers,
rapers, killers,
thieves.
You came alone, in chains.
Without friends nor honor.
You came to us rich,
you came to us poor.
Some of you
bear the names of proud houses.
Others only bastard names,
or no names at all.
It does not matter.
All that...
is in the past.
Here,
on the Wall,
we are all one house.
Tonight,
You're allowed to look happy.
You're going to be a ranger.
Isn't that what you always wanted?
I want to find my uncle.
I know he's alive out there,
I know he is.
I wish I could help you,
but I'm no ranger.
It's the steward life, for me.
The honor of being a steward.
Not much, really.
But there's food...
... and your loves, alike.
Here,
you begin a new.
A man
of the Night's Watch
lives his life
for the realm.
Not for a king,
or a lord,
or the honor of this house
or that house,
not for gold and glory
nor a woman's love,
but for the realm,
and all the people in it.
You've all learned the words
of the vow,
think carefully before you say them.
The penalty for desertion
is death.
You can take your vows here,
tonight,
at sunset.
Do any of you
still keep the Old Gods?
I do, My Lord.
You'll want to take your vow
before a heart tree, as your uncle did?
Yes, My Lord.
You'll find a weirwood
a mile north of the Wall,
and your Old Gods too, maybe.
- Might I go as well?
- Does house Tarly keep the Old Gods?
I was named
in the light of the Seven,
as my father was,
and his father before him.
Why would you forsake
the gods of your father and your house?
The Night's Watch is my house now.
And the Seven
have never answered my prayers.
Perhaps the Old Gods will.
As you wish.
You've all been assigned an order,
according to our needs
and your strengths.
Halder,
to the builders,
Pyp, to the stewards,
Toad, to the builders,
Grenn, to the rangers,
Samwell, to the stewards,
Matthar, to the rangers,
Dareon, to the stewards,
Balian, to the rangers,
Rast, to the rangers,
Jon, to the stewards,
Rancer, to the builder,
Echiel, to the builders,
Gordo, to the stewards,
Niko, to the rangers,
Escan, to the rangers,
Vorcoy, to the builders,
Joby, to the stables,
Mink, to the kitchens,
Allo, to the builders,
Nelugo, to the rangers.
May all the gods preserve you.
Rangers, with me.
Builders.
Samwell.
You will assist me
in the rookery and library.
You will report to Bowen Marsh
in the kitchens.
Report to one-eyed Joe
in the stables.
Dareon,
we're sending you to Eastwatch.
Present yourself to Borcas
when you arrive.
Make no comment about his nose.
The Lord Commander Mormont
requested you for his personal steward.
Will I serve the Lord Commander's meals,
and fetch hot water for his bath?
Certainly.
And keep a fire burning
in his chambers,
change his sheets and blankets daily
and do everything else
the Lord Commander requires of you.
Do you take me for a servant?
We took you
for a man of the Night's Watch.
But perhaps we were wrong in that.
- May I go?
- As you wish.
Wait.
- Don't you see what they're doing?
- I see ser Alliser's revenge.
He wanted it and he got it.
Stewards are nothing but maids.
I'm a better swordsman
than any of you.
- It's not fair.
- Fair?
I was singing for a high lord
when he put his hand on my leg.
And he wanted to see my cock.
I pushed him away and he said
he'd have my hands cut off.
Now I'm here, at the end of the world,
with no one to sing for but old man.
I'll never see my family again.
I'll never be inside a woman again.
So, don't tell me about fair.
I thought you were caught steeling
cheese for your starving sister.
I was gonna tell a bunch of strangers
that a lord tried to grab my cock?
Could you sing me a song, Pyp?
I'd like to hear a song.
Now listen to me.
The old man
is the Lord Commander
of the Night's Watch.
You'll be with him day and night.
Yes, you'll clean his clothes.
But you'll also take his letters,
attend him at meetings,
squire for him in battle.
You'll know everything,
be part of everything.
And he asked for you himself.
He wants to groom you for command.
I always wanted to be a ranger.
I always wanted to be a wizard.
What?
I'm serious.
So, you'll stay
and say your words with me.
A moment.
Alone, if you will.
He named you Protector of the Realm.
He did.
She won't care.
Give me an hour
and I put swords at your command.
What should I do with them?
Strike.
Tonight while the castle sleeps.
We must get Joffrey away
from his mother and into our custody.
Protector of the Realm or no,
who holds the King holds the Kingdom.
Every moment you delay
give Cersei another moment to prepare.
By the time Robert dies,
it will be too late for the both of us.
What about Stannis?
Saving the Seven Kingdoms from Cersei
and delivering them to Stannis?
You have odd notions
about protecting the realm.
- Stannis is your older brother.
- This isn't about the succession.
That didn't matter
when you rebelled against the Mad King.
What's best for the Kingdoms?
What's best for the people we rule?
Well, we all know what Stannis is.
He inspires no love or loyalty.
He's not a King.
I am.
Stannis is a commander.
He has led men into war twice.
He destroyed the Greyjoy fleet.
Yes, he is a good soldier.
So was Robert.
Tell me.
Do you still believe
good soldiers make good kings?
I will not dishonor Robert's last hours
by shedding blood in his halls
and dragging frightened children
from their beds.
You will sail to Dragonstone.
You will place this
in a hand of Stannis Baratheon.
Not his steward.
Not his Captain.
And not his wife.
Only Stannis himself.
Now leave us.
My Lord Protector.
The King has no true born sons.
Joffrey and Tommen
are Jaime Lannister's bastards.
So when the King dies...
The throne passes to his brother.
Lord Stannis.
So it would seem.
- Unless...
- There is no unless.
He is the rightful hair.
Nothing can change that.
He cannot take the throne without you.
You would be wise to deny it to him.
And to make sure Joffrey succeeds.
Do you have a shred of honor?
You are now Hand of the King
and Protector of the Realm.
All the power is yours.
You need only...
reach out and take it.
Make peace with the Lannisters.
Release the Imp.
Wed your daughter to Joffrey.
We've time to get rid of Stannis
and if Joffrey seems likely
to cause problems
when he comes into his throne,
we simply reveal his little secret
and sit Lord Renly there instead.
We?
You'll need someone
to share these burdens, I assure you...
My price would be modest.
What you suggest is treason.
Only if we lose.
Make peace with the Lannisters,
you say.
The people
who tried to murder my boy.
We only make peace
with our enemies, my Lord.
That's why it's called making peace.
I won't do it.
So it will be Stannis, and war.
There is no other choice.
He is the heir.
So why did you call me here?
Not for my wisdom, clearly.
You promised Catelyn you'd help me.
The Queen has a dozen knights
and a hundred men-at-arms.
Enough to overwhelm
what remains of my household guard.
I need the gold cloaks.
The City Watch is two thousand strong
and sworn to defend the King's peace.
Look at you.
You know what you want me to do.
You know it has to be done.
But it's not honorable, so...
The words stick in your throat.
When the Queen proclaims one King,
and the Hand proclaims another,
whose peace
do the gold cloaks protect?
Who do they follow?
The man who pays them.
"Hear my words,
and bear witness to my vow,
"Night gathers,
and now my watch begins.
"It shall not end until my death.
"I shall take no wife,
"hold no lands, father no children.
"I shall wear no crowns
and win no glory.
"I shall live and die at my post.
"I am the sword in the darkness.
"I am the watcher on the walls.
"I am the shield
that guards the realms of men.
"I pledge my life
"and honor to the Night's Watch,
"for this night
and all the nights to come."
You knelt as boys,
rise now as men of the Night's Watch.
What's he got there?
To me, Ghost.
Bring it here.
Gods be good!
What will they do to him?
When the khalasar rides,
he'll be leashed to a saddle,
forced to run behind the horses
for as long as he can.
And when he falls?
I saw a man last nine miles once.
King Robert still wants me dead.
This poisoner was the first.
He won't be the last.
I thought he'd leave me alone,
- now that my brother is gone.
- He will never leave you alone.
If you ride to darkest Asshai,
his assassins will follow you.
If you sailed all the way
to the Basilisk Isles,
his spies would tell him.
He will never abandon the hunt.
You're a Targaryen.
The Last Targaryen.
Your son will have Targaryen blood
with 40,000 riders behind him.
He will not have my son.
He will not have you either,
Khaleesi.
It's all right.
It's all right, let him through.
King Joffrey and the Queen Regent
request your presence.
King Joffrey?
King Robert is gone.
The Gods give him rest.
All is accomplished.
The City Watch is yours.
Good.
Is Lord Renly joining us?
I fear Lord Renly has left the city.
He rode through the Old gate
an hour before dawn
with Ser Loras Tyrell
and some 50 retainers.
Last seen
galloping South in some haste.
We stand behind you, Lord Stark.
All hail His Grace.
Joffrey of Houses Baratheon & Lannister.
The first of his name.
King of the Andals and the first men,
Lord of the Seven Kingdoms
and Protector of the Realm,
I command the Council to make
all arrangements for my coronation.
I wish to be crowned
within the fortnight.
Today,
I shall accept oaths of fealty
from my loyal councilors.
Ser Barristan.
I believe no man here
could ever question your honor.
King Robert's seal.
Unbroken.
Lord Eddard Stark is herein named
Protector of the Realm.
To rule as Regent
until the heir come of age.
May I see that letter, Ser Barristan?
Protector of the Realm.
Is this meant to be your shield,
Lord Stark?
A piece of paper.
Those were the King's words.
We have a new King now.
Lord Eddard, when we last spoke,
you offered me some counsel.
Allow me to return the courtesy.
Bend the knee, my Lord.
Bend the knee
and swear loyalty to my son.
And we shall allow
you to live out your days
in the grey waste you call "Home".
Your son has no claim to the throne.
Liar!
You condemned yourself
with your mouth.
Seize this traitor.
Ser Barristan is a good man, loyal man.
Do him no harm.
He stands alone?
Kill him! Kill all of them!
Commander.
Take the Queen
and her children into custody.
Escort them back to the royal apartments
and keep them there.
Under guard.
Men of the Watch!
I want no bloodshed.
Tell your men to lay down their swords.
No one needs to die.
Now!
I did warn you not to trust me.
lafabrique.fbk (at) gmail.com