"From this time
until the end of time,
we are the free and independent
Kingdom of the North."
You'll give the Starks
our reply, cousin?
I will, Your Grace.
Did you see my brother when you
were the Starks' guest?
I did.
Tell him he's not
been forgotten.
- I'll do it.
- Come, brothers. We'll leave him to it.
Be quick about it.
I've yielded Winterfell
to Prince Theon.
All of you should do
as he commands.
Betray me and you will
wish you hadn't.
All hail the king.
Who threw that?
Get back!
You're all right now, little bird.
You're all right.
Your brothers desert you?
- We'll stop here.
- Think they're out looking for you?
Yes.
What might this be?
Let's go.
Amory Lorch.
Now!
A man will do
what must be done.
Guard!
I have something for you
from Prince Theon.
When I came to this city,
I had nothing.
Today I am the richest
man in Qarth
with no regrets.
Where are they?
Where are my dragons?!
~ Game of Thrones 2x07 ~
~ A Man Without Honor ~
~ Resync by Scofield ~
~ Transcript: www.addic7ed.com ~
~ Timings: www.italiansubs.net
~ www.SubCentral.de ~
~ www.TV4User.de ~
A cripple?
You let a cripple escape?
The boy can't walk,
but somehow
he slipped past you?
The giant must have took him.
The giant?
Hodor?
Oh, well, that's all right, then.
You let a halfwit
escape with a cripple.
And Rickon, too?
The little one?
Gone along with
the wildling woman,
the one you were fucking.
Right, get the horses
and the hounds.
Come on, find the scent.
Come on,
where they going?
Halt!
Enjoying
your first hunt?
So far, hunting seems very similar
to riding, My Lord.
With hunting,
there's blood at the end.
They're little boys.
I was a little boy
when I was torn away from
my home and brought here.
So I kept my word.
I never ran away.
If I find them soon enough,
I won't hurt them.
Well, I'll hurt them,
but I won't kill them.
Those boys are of far more value
to you alive than dead.
They have no value
to me missing.
Robb will have sent a force
to retake Winterfell by now.
Robb's in the Riverlands.
My sister's in Deepwood Motte.
She'll get here long before they do.
And Ned Stark always said
500 men could hold
Winterfell against 10,000.
We have a scent!
The hounds have the scent.
Come, Maester,
don't look so grim.
It's all just a game.
We should have took more food.
We couldn't risk going to the kitchens.
Those people all love you. They would
have given you whatever you needed.
And if Theon found out,
he'd hang them.
- The boy can't survive on walnuts.
- I'm fine.
We've been walking
since before sunrise.
- Even Hodor will tire.
- Hodor.
- Even you, sweet giant.
-  Hodor.
Wait, I know that farm.
I sent those two
Winterfell orphans there.
Jack and Billy.
They'll give us some food.
We can't risk it.
If Theon tracks us here,
he'll torture them
until he finds out
where we are.
Billy climbs a tree
better than anyone.
You've never seen me
climb a tree, little man.
They'll be after us
with hounds.
We got a good start
on them,
but we can't outrun
hounds forever.
Did you pull a knife
on me in the night?
What's the matter?
Can't be the first time you pressed
your bone against a woman's ass.
Let's move.
Oh, it is the first time.
How old are you, boy?
I'm a man of the Night's Watch.
You're a boy who's
never been with a girl.
Don't your stones start to hurt
if your bone never gets--
Don't call them that.
What, stones?
Or bone?
Neither.
Both.
Move!
I heard they get
all swollen
and bruised if you
don't use them.
Of course, maybe that's
just what the lads say
when they want me
feeling sorry for them.
As if I'd feel
sorry for them.
Are there no girl crows?
There are no women
of the Night's Watch, no.
So the lads just do it
with each other?
No.
- Never?
- Never.
We swore an oath.
You have sheep
at the Wall?
With your hands, then?
No wonder
you're all so miserable.
Would you please shut up?
You think you're
better than me, crow.
- I'm a free woman--
- You're a free woman?
I might be your prisoner,
but I'm a free woman.
If you're my prisoner,
you're not a free woman.
That's what
"prisoner" means.
And you think you're free?
You swore
some stupid oath
and now you can never
touch a girl.
It was my choice
to say the words.
- So you don't like girls?
- Of course I like girls.
But you chose
never to touch them.
That's the price you pay if you want
to be a man of the Night's Watch.
So instead of getting
naked with a girl,
- you'd prefer to invade our lands--
- Invade your lands?
Wildlings raid
our lands all the time.
Some of them tried to kill my
little brother, a crippled boy!
They're not your lands!
We've been here
the whole time.
You lot came along
and just put up a big wall
and said it was yours.
My father was Ned Stark.
I have the blood
of the First Men.
My ancestors lived here,
same as yours.
So why are you
fighting us?
Go on.
Now I want you to tell me
what happened.
Come on, this way.
Come on, speak up. Speak up.
Wolfsbane...
a rare substance.
This is no common assassin.
We hanged 20 men last night.
I don't care if you hanged 100.
A man tried to kill me.
I want his name and I want his head.
We think it was an infiltrator
from the Brotherhood Without Banners.
Pretentious name for a band of outlaws.
We can't allow rebels behind our lines
to harass us with impunity.
We look like fools and they look like heroes.
That's how kings fall.
I want them dead, every one.
Killing them isn't the problem.
It's finding them.
Have you gone soft, Clegane?
I always thought you had
a talent for violence.
Burn the villages, burn the farms.
Let them know what it means
to choose the wrong side.
Is that mutton?
Yes, My Lord.
Don't like mutton.
I'll bring something else.
Leave it.
Are you hungry?
- No.
- Of course you are.
Eat.
I'll eat in the kitchen later.
It's bad manners to refuse
a Lord's offer.
Sit.
Eat.
You're small for your age.
I suppose you've been underfed
your whole life.
I eat a lot.
I just don't grow.
This will be my last war,
win or lose.
Have you ever lost before?
Do you think I'd be in my position
if I had lost a war?
But this is the one I'll be remembered for.
The "War of Five Kings" they're calling it.
My legacy will be determined
in the coming months.
Do you know what legacy means?
It's what you pass down to your children
and your children's children.
It's what remains of you when you're gone.
Harren the Black thought this castle
would be his legacy.
The greatest fortress ever built...
the tallest towers, the strongest walls.
The Great Hall had 35 hearths.
35. Can you imagine?
Look at it now...
a blasted ruin.
Do you know what happened?
Dragons?
Yes...
Dragons happened.
Harrenhal was built to withstand
an attack from the land.
A million men could have
marched on these walls
and a million men would
have been repelled.
But an attack from the air
with dragon fire...
Harren and all his sons
roasted alive within these walls.
Aegon Targaryen changed the rules.
That's why every child alive
still knows his name
300 years after his death.
Aegon and his sisters.
It wasn't just Aegon riding his dragon.
It was Rhaenys and Visenya, too.
Correct.
A student of history, are you?
Rhaenys rode Meraxes.
Visenya rode Vhagar.
I'm sure I knew that when I was a boy.
Visenya Targaryen was a great warrior.
She had a Valyrian steel sword
she called Dark Sister.
She's a heroine of yours, I take it?
Aren't most girls more interested
in the pretty maidens from the songs?
Jonquil with the flowers in her hair?
- Most girls are idiots.
- Ha!
You remind me of my daughter.
Where did you learn all this stuff
about Visenya and her Valyrian Steel sword?
From my father.
He was a well-read stonemason.
Can't say I've ever met
a literate stonemason.
Have you met many stonemasons, My Lord?
Careful now, girl.
I enjoy you, but be careful.
Take that back to the kitchen.
Eat what you want.
And, girl.
M'lord.
Lowborn girls say "M'lord,"
not "My Lord."
If you're going to pose as a commoner,
you should do it properly.
My mother served Lady Dustin
for many years, My Lord.
She taught me how to speak proper...
properly.
You're too smart for your own good.
Has anyone told you that?
Yes.
Go on.
I beg pardon, Ser.
I should have come to you after
to thank you for saving me.
You were so brave.
Brave?
A dog doesn't need courage
to chase off rats.
Does it give you joy to scare people?
No. It gives me joy to kill people.
Spare me. You can't tell me Lord Eddard
Stark of Winterfell never killed a man.
It was his duty. He never liked it.
Is that what he told you?
He lied.
Killing is the sweetest thing there is.
Why are you always so hateful?
You'll be glad of the hateful things I do
someday when you're queen
and I'm all that stands between
you and your beloved king.
I've demanded a meeting of the Thirteen.
One of them did this or knows who did.
You are one of the Thirteen.
If I wanted your dragons,
I would have taken them.
They mean nothing to me on their own.
Nothing?
They're more valuable than
anything in the world.
Shall we look inside my vault and see
what selling your dragons
would buy me I cannot buy already?
We will get them back.
There is no we,
so why would you help me get them back?
I took you under my protection
in front of the rulers of my city.
A man is what others say
he is and no more.
If they say that Xaro Xhoan Daxos is a liar,
my word is worth nothing.
I cannot let this thing
happen to you under my roof.
But it did happen under your roof.
Khaleesi...
many times in my life I have been...
I don't care where you've been.
You think we're savages because
we don't live in stone castles.
We can't make steel as good
as yours, it's true, but...
We're free.
If someone tried to tell us we couldn't lie down
as man and woman,
we'd shove a spear up his ass.
We don't go serving some shit king
who's only king because his father was.
No.
No, you serve Mance Rayder,
the King-Beyond-the-Wall.
We chose Mance Rayder to lead us.
He was a crow, same as you,
but he wanted to be free.
You could be free, too.
You don't need to live your whole life
taking commands from old men.
Wake up when you want to wake up.
I could show you the streams
to fish, the woods to hunt.
Build yourself a cabin and find
a woman to lie with in the night.
You're a pretty lad.
The girls would claw each other's
eyes out to get naked with you.
Walk.
I could teach you how to do it.
I know how to do it.
You know nothing, Jon Snow.
And what did she say?
She admired your spirit, Your Grace.
And what then?
She, uh...
If every man were held accountable for the
actions of every distant relative, Ser Alton,
we'd all hang.
She tore the paper in half, Your Grace.
You've acted with honor.
I thank you for it.
Lord Karstark, see that
Ser Alton's pen is clean.
And give him a hot supper.
Ser Alton's pen is occupied, Your Grace.
The prisoners from the Yellow Fork.
Too many prisoners.
Is there room for Ser Alton?
Does he need to lie down?
Have the men build him a new pen.
Put him in with the Kingslayer for now.
Have your boy watch over them.
Torrhen.
That will be all.
Your Grace.
A minute of your time?
I've been treating your wounded men.
And my enemies as some of my bannermen
are fond of mentioning.
They're not my enemies.
That's what I tell my bannermen.
I've already run through the
supplies I brought with me.
Some are easily replaced...
egg yolks, turpentine, oil of roses.
But some are not.
I need silk for stitching.
I need fennel root
for those with fever, willow bark.
Mostly I need milk of the poppy.
You saw what it was like
to amputate a foot without any.
I assume there will be more loss of limb
before this war is over.
- If you need help finding these...
- I know where to find them.
I'm sorry, I shouldn't interrupt you.
Continue, My Lady.
You're riding to the Crag
to negotiate a surrender?
Yes.
The Crag will have a Maester
and he will have what I need.
I expect he will.
If I could write a list...
come with me to the Crag.
- I don't think that will be...
- Let the Maester show you his stores.
I want the wounded men
to be treated well...
all the wounded men.
Children, come inside, quick.
Hurry up!
Can't find anything, Ser.
- They've lost the scent.
- Try again.
We've circled this farmhouse twice.
There's no sign of them.
We could start the search fresh
in the morning, My Lord.
I'm looking at spending the rest of life
being treated like a fool and a eunuch
by my own people.
Ask yourself, "Is there anything I wouldn't do
to stop that from happening?"
The hounds will find the scent again.
I'll beat them until they do.
I'll whip every man here
until I have both those boys in hand.
And once I've got them,
the pampered little shits...
It's better to be cruel than weak.
Prince Theon.
- Where are they?
- Who, m'lord?
The Stark boys. Where are they?
I don't know. I seen no one.
Oh!
Think harder.
I swear, m'lord,
I don't know.
My Lord,
over here.
I think I've found what
we're looking for.
Send the old man home.
Go back to Winterfell.
Take him back.
Theon, don't do this.
You came back.
As soon as I heard.
Do you know anything?
Irri is dead.
I know.
- She was a good...
- she's dead.
She died alone.
She died for me and I couldn't protect her.
Doreah?
We can't find her.
She must be dead, too.
I led my people out of the Red Waste
and into the slaughterhouse.
I should have been here.
You went to find me a ship.
My place is by your side.
I shouldn't have left you alone
with these people.
These people?
They are not to be trusted.
And who is to be trusted?
Who are my people?
The Targaryens?
I only knew one... my brother,
and he would have let 1,000 men rape me
if it had got him the crown.
The Dothraki?
Most of them turned on me the day
that Khal Drogo fell from his horse.
Your people are in Westeros.
The people in Westeros
don't know I'm alive.
- They will soon enough.
- And then what?
They'll pray for my return?
They'll wave dragon banners
and shout my name?
That's what my brother believed
and he was a fool.
You are not your brother.
Trust me, Khaleesi.
There it is...
"trust me."
And it's you I should trust, Ser Jorah?
Only you?
I don't need trust any longer.
I don't want it and
I don't have room for it.
- You are too young to be so...
- And you are too familiar.
Forgive me, Khaleesi.
No one can survive
in this world without help.
No one.
Let me help you, please.
Tell me how.
Find my dragons.
How long till we get back to your crows?
We're close.
What, a day?
A half-day?
You don't know, do you?
- Do you even know where they are?
- We're close.
What do you think they'll say
when they hear about you and me?
Nothing happened between you and me.
"I swear it, old master king crow, Ser,
we were only close together for warmth.
And then I felt it,
right up against me backside like a club.
I can show you the bruise on me tailbone.
And before I knew what
was where, his... his...
well, it was all out in the open,
all angry as you like.
And I didn't want to want it,
but, oh, I did!
And he spread me legs and... ruined.
The shame of it.
Now I can never marry
a perfumed lord.
What will me poor savage father say?"
Turn back around.
"And I thought that we were done,
but he said,
'Turn back around.'"
I'll tell you what, Jon Snow,
since it's going to be your
word against mine,
and since you can't talk
about it without blushing,
we may as well just.
What, right here in the muck?
I'll keep you warm enough.
Are you that afraid of it?
- That's enough.
- Oh, it's nice
and wet and warm.
Enough
It don't have teeth.
All right!
All right.
Gods, you're dull.
Should have took me while
you had the chance.
No!
no!
Oh, no.
It's all right.
- Give me that.
- If the queen sees
I can have Joffrey's children now...
Help me flip it over.
- Where are you going?
- To tell her Grace.
You'll say nothing to anyone.
Do you understand?
Your mother might have prepared you.
You flowered, my dear. No more.
My mother told me, but I
thought it would be different.
In what way?
I thought it would be less...
less messy.
Wait until you bear the child.
You're a woman now.
Do you have any idea what that means?
I'm fit to bear children for the king?
A prospect that once delighted you...
bringing little princes
and princesses into the world,
the greatest honor for a queen.
Joffrey has always been difficult.
Even his birth, I labored a day and a half
to bring him into this world.
You cannot imagine the pain.
I screamed so loudly, I was sure
Robert would hear me in the Kingswood.
His Grace was not with you?
Robert was hunting.
That was his custom.
Whenever my time was near,
my royal husband would flee
to the trees with his
huntsmen and his hounds.
And when he returned, he would present me
with some pelts or a stag's head,
and I would present him with a baby.
Not that I wanted him there, mind you.
I had Grand Maester Pycelle,
an army of midwives,
and I had my brother.
When they told Jaime he wasn't
allowed in the birthing room,
he smiled and asked which one of them
proposed to keep him out.
Joffrey will show you no such devotion.
You may never love the king,
but you will love his children.
I love his Grace with all my heart.
That's so very touching to hear.
Permit me to share some
womanly wisdom with you
on this very special day.
The more people you love,
the weaker you are.
You'll do things for them that
you know you shouldn't do.
You'll act the fool to make them
happy, to keep them safe.
Love no one but your children.
On that front, a mother has no choice.
But... shouldn't I love Joffrey,
Your Grace?
You can try,
little dove.
Who did you say your mother was again?
Cinda Lannister.
Is she the fat one?
Well, perhaps she's gotten
a little larger than she...
No, no. There's only one fat Lannister.
If she was your mother, you'd know it.
I... I squired for you once, you know?
When?
The tournament the day of
Willem Frey's wedding.
I went to Willem Frey's wedding?
You did.
Your squire had gotten
so drunk the night before that he...
He threw up on his horse
on the way to the tourney grounds.
What was his name?
Bryan.
Poor lad.
That was my brother's doing,
I seem to recall.
I remember you.
You had never squired for anyone before.
That's right. I ran up and volunteered.
"Let me, My Lord. Let me."
My father was furious,
afraid I'd embarrass our family in front of
the family.
You didn't, though.
- You really remember?
- Mm.
You knew when you were needed
and when to go away.
It's a rare talent.
Most of my squires,
they mean well, but young men
with big jobs, they
tend to overdo them.
Well, when I think back to that day...
You were saying?
I...
never mind.
- It's embarrassing.
- More embarrassing
than being chained to a post
covered in your own shit?
I remember everything about that day...
your helmet, your horse,
the rake line in the dirt along the list,
where the sun was in the sky
when you knocked Balon Swann from his horse,
and the dent in your shield
when you handed it back to me.
I'll remember it all until I die.
That was the best day of my life.
And I remember being on the field
after it was over.
All the competitors were done.
I was the last one out there.
And I couldn't leave.
I couldn't bring myself to go and sit
with my family at a table so
far on the edge of the feast
you could barely even see the bride.
And I couldn't bear to tell them
what it had been like squiring for you
when I knew that they could never have the
faintest idea what I was talking about.
I understand completely.
How could you?
S-sorry, I...
- I didn't mean to doubt you. It's just that I...
- I was 16 once.
I also had to replace someone's
squire on short notice.
Which knight was it?
Barristan Selmy.
The fight against the Kingswood outlaws.
Before your time.
What was he like?
He was
a painter,
a painter who only used red.
I couldn't imagine being
able to fight like that,
not back then.
And to help him do that, to be a part
of something that perfect...
I don't need to explain
how that felt, not to you.
- It's hard to put into words.
- It's like stepping into a dream
you've been dreaming for as long as you can
remember and finding out that the dream
is more real than your life.
Leaving that battlefield was
like being dragged off to prison.
- Did you squire for him again?
- No.
I didn't have your gift.
He couldn't take a step
without stepping on me.
I was awful, a complete liability...
until...
one of the outlaws decided
to take on a 16-year-old squire.
It's a good thing I am who I am.
I'd have been useless at anything else.
I'm not well-suited for imprisonment.
Shocking, I know.
Some men are.
Ned Stark...
I imagine he made an excellent
prisoner right up until the end.
But me, though...
my life has left me uniquely
unfit for constraint.
Have you thought about...?
- Of course. Every day.
- And?
Good prisoners breed
good jailers, apparently.
The Starks are very careful.
But there is a way, I think.
It wasn't possible until now.
What is it?
- It's actually quite simple.
- Well, let me help you.
You'll only have to do one thing.
Tell me.
You'll have to die.
Jorah the Andal.
This man must sail past old Valyria.
All who travel too close to
the Doom must have protection.
- I didn't come here for lessons.
- No, you came for the dragons.
You have them?
Where are they?
Draw your sword.
See what your steel is worth.
You want to please the Mother of Dragons.
You love her.
Where are the dragons?
Will you betray her again,
Jorah the Andal?
Will you betray her again?
Never.
The thief you seek
is with her now.
I did not leave the comfort of my home
to come to yours and be called a thief.
No one is calling you a thief.
Who is she to accuse us?
- Please, they're my children. I'm begging you.
- Begging us?
It wasn't very long ago
you were threatening us.
Without me, the dragons will die.
It will be for the best.
Your dragons will bring the world
nothing but death and misery, my dear.
If I knew where they were,
I would not tell you.
You are cruel, my friend.
The mother of dragons is in the right.
She must be reunited with her babies.
I will help you, Khaleesi.
How?
I will take you to the House of the Undying
where I have put them.
You have my dragons?
When I learned you were
coming to our city,
I made an arrangement
with the King of Qarth.
He procured them for me.
But there is no King of Qarth.
There is now.
That was the other half of the arrangement.
You would keep your gates
and your minds closed
to everything outside your walls,
but Qarth cannot remain the greatest city
that ever was if it refuses to change.
I will open Qarth to the world
as I have forced it to open itself to me.
Your ambition is an inspiration.
But like all upstarts, you overreach.
Three dragons the size of cats
and an alliance with a charlatan
do not make you a king.
An upstart and a charlatan?
Empires have been built by less.
Those on the margins
often come to control the center,
and those in the center
make room for them,
willingly or otherwise.
The Mother of Dragons
will be with her babies.
She will give them her love
and they will thrive by her side...
forever.
A mother should be with her children.
Where will you run to,
Daenerys Stormborn?
Your dragons wait for you
in the House of the Undying.
Come see them.
- Lady Stark!
- No farther.
Keep your hands off me, woman.
Don't enter without an invitation, man.
Forgive me. Lady Stark.
- What is it?
- They caught the Kingslayer.
- Kill the fucking Kingslayer!
- Hang him!
You'll die today.
Justice for the Karstark.
Gut him!
Get back! I want his head!
Any man who stands between a father
and his vengeance asks for death.
Lord Karstark,
this man is our prisoner.
- This monster killed my son.
- And crippled mine.
He will answer for his crimes,
I promise you, but not here.
I will have his head.
- And if you try and stop me...
- You will strike me down?
Have you forgotten me, Ser?
I am the widow of your liege Lord Eddark Stark.
I am the mother of your king!
- And where is our king now?
- You know very well.
He has gone to the Crag
to accept the surrender.
Aye, gone to the Crag,
but not to negotiate.
- He brought that foreign bitch with him.
- How dare you?
Threatening My Lady is an act of treason.
Treason?
How can it be treason to kill Lannisters?
I understand your grief, My Lord...
better than most I understand it...
but in the name of my son,
the King in the North,
stand down.
When your son returns,
I will demand this murderer's head.
Wise men do not make demands of kings.
Fathers who love their sons do.
I will have his head.
Thank you for fighting
on my behalf, Lady Stark.
I would have come to your defense, but...
Take him to the stockades.
Bind him with every chain you can find!
You've become a real she-wolf
in your later years.
- There's not much fish left in you.
- And gag him!
Since when do you light your own candles?
Since I decided that I can't stand to look
at any of my handmaidens for another instant.
How many times can you
read one raven scroll?
Stannis Baratheon's fleet
has been spotted sailing north
past Tarth... 200 ships.
- More than we have.
- Yes, that's more than we have.
He'll be at our gates within five days,
four if he has the wind.
We have strong, high walls.
We'll rain fire down on them from above.
"Rain fire on them from above."
You're quoting father, aren't you?
Why not?
He has a good mind for strategy,
doesn't he?
We call it tactics, not strategy.
But, yes, he does have a good mind for it.
The best mind, some would say.
Sadly, he's not here.
It's just you, me, and Joffrey,
the Lord of the Seven Kingdoms
and protector of the realm.
- I'm sure you'll make a point eventually.
- He needs to start acting like a king.
This war you started is coming
to our doorstep.
And if the entire city
wants Joffrey dead...
I'm not the one giving the boy
whores to abuse.
- I thought the girls might help him.
- Did you?
I was wrong.
If we can't control him...
Do you think I haven't tried?
He doesn't listen to me.
It's hard to put a leash on a dog
once you've put a crown on its head.
I always hoped he'd be like Jaime.
He looks like him...
in a certain light.
The boy is more Robert than Jaime.
Robert was a drunken fool,
but he didn't enjoy cruelty.
Sometimes I wonder...
What?
If this is the price
for what we've done,
for our sins.
Sins? The Targaryens...
Wed brother and sister for hundreds of years,
I know.
That's what Jaime and I would say to
each other in our moments of doubt.
It's what I told Ned Stark when he
was stupid enough to confront me.
Half the Targaryens went mad, didn't they?
What's the saying?
Every time a Targaryen is born,
the Gods flip a coin.
You've beaten the odds.
Tommen and Myrcella are good,
decent children, both of them.
- Why wait?
- We're sworn to the king.
- There's not a king.
- That's treason.
So is saving Lannisters, yeah?
- Back off, you.
- No, I won't.
Your son returns at dawn, My Lady?
So they say.
The Kingslayer won't last the night.
Why don't say king Robb.
The more they drink,
the angrier they'll get.
And when the Karstarks
draw their swords...
who wants to die defending a Lannister?
Come.
I need to be alone with him.
- My Lady, our orders...
- your orders, which I just gave you,
are to leave me alone with him.
Come to say goodbye, Lady Stark?
I believe it's my last night
in this world.
Is that a woman?
Do you hear them out there?
They want your head.
Well, old Lord Karstark
doesn't seem to like me.
You strangled his son with your chains.
Was he the one on guard duty?
He was in my way.
- Any Knight would have done the same.
- You are no Knight.
You have forsaken every
vow you ever took.
So many vows.
They make you swear and swear.
Defend the king, obey the king,
obey your father,
protect the innocent,
defend the weak.
But what if your father
despises the king?
What if the king massacres the innocent?
It's too much.
No matter what you do,
you're forsaking one vow or another.
Where did you find this beast?
She is a truer Knight
than you will ever be,
- Kingslayer.
What a king he was.
Here's to Aerys Targaryen,
the second of his name, Lord of the
Seven Kingdoms, Protector of the realm,
and to the sword I shoved in his back.
You are a man without honor.
Do you know
I've never been with any woman but Cersei?
So in my own way,
I have more honor than
poor old dead Ned.
What was the name of that
bastard so in he fathered?
- Brienne.
- No, that wasn't it.
Snow, a bastard from the North.
Now, when... when good old Ned
came home with some whore's baby,
did you pretend to love it?
No.
You're not very good at pretending.
You're an honest woman.
You hated that boy, didn't you?
How could you not hate him?
The walking, talking reminder
that the honorable Lord Eddard Stark
fucked another woman.
Your sword.
I told you what would happen.
All of you...
I told you what would happen
if you served me loyally...
and what would happen if you did not.
What are you doing?
- If there's any who still question...
- What have you done?
whether your new lord
means what he says...
Here is the answer to your question.
No!
~ www.TV4User.de ~
~ www.SubCentral.de ~