You're accused of killing the king.
I didn't do it.
Which is why we're having a trial.
One of my three judges is my father.
Mace Tyrell will serve as the second judge.
I want you to be the third.
I will also invite you to sit
on the Small Council.
I never realized you had
such respect for Dorne.
What good is power if you cannot
protect the ones you love?
You can avenge them.
You really believe
Tyrion murdered your son?
You're still interested
in being queen, I take it?
It would be a great honor.
But I will have to speak
to my father about it.
I will speak to mine.
You started wars
to protect this family's future.
Tyrion deserves
for lighting our future to fire.
What kind of knight beats a helpless girl?
The kind who serves his king.
The next time Ser Meryn speaks,
kill him.
How many Hands have you betrayed,
Pycelle?
- I am loyal servant!
- Throw him in one of the black cells.
Oh no, no, no, no.
There are many who know that without you,
this city faced certain defeat.
The king won't give you any honors,
but we will not forget.
The city is yours.
All these people are your subjects now.
Sometimes it is better
to answer injustice with mercy.
I will answer injustice with justice.
"Find a special gift.
"Theon's favorite toy.
"He cried when I took it away from him."
I'm going to pick
the fastest ship in our fleet.
and I'm going to bring him home.
We need to look East for ships and men.
- Soldiers win wars.
- We don't have any gold.
I'm running out of time, Ser Davos,
which means you're running out of time.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Your Grace, if you'd like
to sit, I'm sure that...
We've been here since midday.
Easterners have a difference
sense of time, I've often found.
Once I was waiting for Salladhor
Saan here in Braavos.
Together, we were going to run
three shiploads
of the finest...
Welcome to the Iron Bank.
Please, sit.
What can we do
for you, Lord Stannis?
This is Stannis
of the House Baratheon,
King of the Andals
and the First Men,
Lord of the Seven Kingdoms
and Protector of the Realm.
The Iron Throne
is currently occupied
by Tommen
of the House Baratheon,
King of the Andals
and the First Men,
Lord of the Seven Kingdoms
and Protector of the Realm.
He shares no blood with me.
He is a bastard born of incest.
As was his brother before him.
Yes, we have heard this story.
It's not a story.
It's the truth.
The king's grandfather
tells a different story.
A story about a jealous uncle
whose attempts to usurp the
throne from the rightful king
cost the Seven Kingdoms
dearly in blood and gold.
Gold you loaned him.
And you feel your blood gives
you a claim on our gold?
More than any man living.
Across the Narrow Sea,
your books are filled
with words like
"usurper" and "madman"
and "blood right."
Here, our books
are filled with numbers.
We prefer the stories they tell.
More plain.
Less open to interpretation.
How many fighting men
remain loyal to you?
4,000.
And how many ships do you have?
The ones still afloat,
Ser Davos,
not at the bottom
of Blackwater Bay.
32.
And how much wheat
and barley and beef
and pork do you produce
on Dragonstone
to feed your 4,000 men
on your 32 ships?
None.
You can see why these numbers
seem unlikely to add up
to a happy ending
from our perspective.
I'm afraid we must respectfully
decline your request.
But we thank you for paying
us the honor of your visit.
My lord.
I'm not a lord,
Ser Davos Seaworth.
You would not be either here.
In Braavos,
thieves are not
rewarded with titles.
Well, strictly speaking,
I didn't do the thieving.
That would be the pirates.
I just moved what they stole
from one place to another.
This is the payment
that was demanded
by King Stannis for my crimes.
I consider it
an honest accounting.
He's an honest man
and he's your best chance
to get back the money
you've sunk into Westeros.
Which is a lot, I imagine.
Wars are expensive.
The war is over.
As long as Stannis lives,
the war is not over.
Who's the real power
in King's Landing?
- Ser Davos...
- Humor me.
-  Tywin Lannister.
- How old is Tywin Lannister?
- 67.
- 67. And when he dies, who's in command?
A half-grown boy,
the product of incest?
Cersei Lannister, a queen
whose people despise her?
Jaime Lannister, a man best
known for killing the king
he was sworn to protect?
When Tywin's gone,
who do you back?
That is a problem
for another time.
Begging your pardon,
I think it's a problem for now.
There's only one reliable
leader left in Westeros.
Stannis.
He's got the birthright.
He's in his prime.
He's a tried and tested
battle commander.
And he doesn't just talk
about paying people back,
he does it.
The lookout sees a
pirate ship sailing their way.
The captain shouts
to his first mate,
"Bring me
my red shirt."
The first mate brings the red
shirt and the captain puts it on.
And when the pirates
try to board,
the brave captain leads
his men to victory.
A few days later,
the lookout screams,
"Two pirate ships!"
The crew is shivering
like scared mice.
But the courageous
captain hollers,
"Bring me
my red shirt!"
After the battle,
the first mate asks,
"Captain, why do you call for
your red shirt before battle?"
The captain replies,
"So that if I am stabbed,
you will not see me bleed."
The next morning
the lookout screams,
"10 pirate ships!
We are surrounded!"
The crew goes silent.
They all look
to their brave captain,
waiting for his usual command.
Calm as ever,
the captain bellows...
"Bring me my brown pants!"
You think they ever met a pirate
who didn't tell them that joke?
Davos.
I heard you were rotting in
a dungeon in Dragonstone.
Only half rotted.
Join us, my friend.
Join us.
This is Lhara.
- And this is...
- I am Lhara.
She's an artist,
this one, truly.
No time, I'm afraid.
We sail at sunrise.
We?
You, me... we.
Once I thought
this man loved me.
Now I know he despises me.
He wants to see me die poor
and alone on some cold...
You won't be alone.
And you won't be poor.
There's a chest of the good
stuff left back at your house.
I gave it to your wife.
You're not my friend, my friend.
I'll see you at sunrise.
"I give you
until the full moon
to order all ironborn
scum out of the North
and back to those shit-stained
rocks you call home.
On the first night
of the full moon,
I will hunt down every
islander still on our lands
and flay them living,
the way I flayed
the 20 ironborn scum
I found at Winterfell.
In the box you'll find
a special gift...
Theon's favorite toy.
He cried when I took
it away from him.
Leave the North now
or more boxes will follow
with more Theon.
Signed Ramsay Snow,
natural born son
of Roose Bolton,
Lord of the Dreadfort
and Warden of the North."
Yes!
They skinned our countrymen
and they mutilated my brother,
your prince.
Your prince.
Everything they've done to him,
they've also done to you.
Yes! Yes!
As long as they can hurt
our prince with impunity,
the word ironborn means nothing.
Go left.
- Theon Greyjoy.
- I don't know...
I'm here for Theon Greyjoy.
Take me to the dungeons.
He's not in the dungeons.
- Last cage on the right.
- Thank you.
This way!
We're going home.
No!
It's all right.
It's me, Yara.
You can't trick me.
Tell him. Tell him you
couldn't trick me.
I'm not tricking you, Theon.
I'm saving you.
Not Theon! Reek!
- Reek! My name is Reek!
-  They're here.
If they catch us
in here, we're trapped.
Help me with him.
No, you can't!
- You can't!
- You're Theon Greyjoy.
No, I don't believe her!
I know who I am!
I'm Reek! Reek!
Loyal Reek!
Good Reek!
I've always been Reek!
This is turning into
a lovely evening.
I'm Reek!
Loyal Reek!
Aah!
Theon!
Give me my broth You've got
bigger balls than he ever did.
But with those big balls
of yours...
how fast can you run?
Make for the ship, now.
But your brother.
My brother is dead.
I have a treat for you.
A reward.
Reward?
Yes, Reek.
Those creatures
who came in the night,
they wanted to take you away.
And you didn't let them.
You remained loyal.
I... I didn't want
them to take me.
I was so scared.
- I didn't want them...
- Yes, yes, Reek.
It's a bath.
For you.
Remove those rags.
Now.
The britches, too, Reek.
Take them off.
Do you love me, Reek?
Yes, of course, my lord.
Good.
Because I need you
to do something for me.
Something very important.
There's a castle, you see.
Some bad men hold this castle.
I need your help
to take this castle back.
But how can...
I need you to play a role.
To pretend to be someone
you're not.
Pretend to be who?
Theon Greyjoy.
_
He is a goatherd.
He says he prayed for your victory
against the slave masters.
I thank him for his prayers.
It was your dragons, he says.
They came this morning
for his flock.
He hopes he has not
offended Your Grace,
but now he has nothing.
Tell this man I am sorry
for his hardship.
I cannot bring back his goats,
but I will see he is paid
their value three times over.
Send the next one in.
_
Queen Daenerys.
Tales of your beauty
were not exaggerated.
I thank you.
Mine is one of the oldest and
proudest families in Meereen.
Then it is my honor
to receive you.
My father, one of
Meereen's most respected
and beloved citizens,
oversaw the restoration
and maintenance
of its greatest landmarks.
This pyramid included.
For that, he has my gratitude.
I should be honored to meet him.
You have, Your Grace.
You crucified him.
I pray you'll never live to see
a member of your family
treated so cruelly.
Your father crucified
innocent children.
My father spoke out against
crucifying those children.
He decried it as a criminal
act, but was overruled.
Is it justice to answer
one crime with another?
I am sorry you no longer
have a father,
but my treatment
of the masters was no crime.
You'd be wise to remember that.
What's done is done.
You are the queen and I
am a servant of Meereen.
A servant who does not wish to
see its traditions eradicated.
And what traditions
do you speak of?
The tradition of funeral rite.
Proper burial in
the Temple of the Graces.
My father and 162
noble Meereenese
are still nailed to those posts,
carrion for vultures,
rotting in the sun.
Your Grace, I ask that you
order these men taken down
so that they might receive
proper burials.
And what of the slave children
these noble Meereenese crucified?
They were rotting
in the sun as well.
Would you have begged me for
their right to a proper burial?
Your Grace, I cannot defend
the actions of the masters.
I can only speak to you as a
son who loved his father.
Let me take his body down.
Let me have him brought
to the temple
and buried with dignity
so that he might find
peace in the next world.
Bury your father,
Hizdahr zo Loraq.
Thank you, my queen.
How many more?
There are 212 supplicants
waiting, Your Grace.
212?
Send the next one in.
These meetings aren't always going
to be this early, are they?
I was up late last night.
So, does this mean I am a
master of something now?
Coins, ships?
Lord Tywin and I
already determined
that I shall be the Master
of Ships long before you...
Lord Tywin, it's a great honor
to have been granted a
seat on this council. I...
The trial
begins this afternoon.
We only have the morning
for affairs of state.
Shall we begin?
Sandor Clegane
has been spotted
in the Riverlands, my lord.
A coward and a traitor.
My birds tell me the Hound
slaughtered five of our soldiers.
I believe the phrase
"fuck the king" was uttered.
Disgraceful.
What would it take
to make the common soldier
stupid enough to try
his luck with the Hound?
10 silver stags
seems a generous bounty.
Make it 100.
What else?
More whispers
from the east, my lord.
The Targaryen girl?
Daenerys has taken up
residence in Meereen.
She has conquered the city
and rules as its queen.
Conquered with what?
She commands an army
of Unsullied, my queen.
Some 8,000 strong.
She has a company
of sellswords...
the Second Sons.
She has two knights
advising her...
Jorah Mormont
and Barristan Selmy.
And she has three dragons.
Baby dragons.
Larger every year, Your Grace.
Mormont is spying on her for us.
No longer. He appears
to be fully devoted to her.
As for Ser Barristan,
it would seem
he took his dismissal
from the Kingsguard
a bit harder than anticipated.
He's an old man.
He wasn't fit to protect my son.
Joffrey didn't die on his watch.
Dismissing him was as
insulting as it was stupid.
Don't tell me you're worried about
a child halfway across the world.
A child with two seasoned
warriors counseling her
and a powerful army
at her back, Your Grace.
Lord Varys is right.
I have been to Essos and seen
the Unsullied firsthand.
They are very impressive
on the battlefield.
Less so in the bedroom.
Dragons haven't won
a war in 300 years.
Armies win them all the time.
She must be dealt with.
How, my lord?
By force?
Eventually, if it comes to that.
Can your little birds
find their way into Meereen?
Most certainly, my Lord Hand.
Mmm. Lord Tyrell,
be a good man.
Fetch my quill and paper.
Prince Oberyn.
Lord Varys...
Only Varys.
I'm not actually a nobleman.
No one is under obligation
to call me lord.
And yet everyone does.
You seem quite knowledgeable
about the Unsullied.
Did you spend much time
in Essos?
Five years.
May I ask why?
'Tis a big and beautiful world.
Most of us live and die
in the same corner
where we were born
and never get to see any of it.
I don't want to be most of us.
Most of us aren't princes.
You are from Essos.
Where? Lys?
I have an ear for accents.
I've lost my accent entirely.
I have an ear for that as well.
How did you get here?
It's a long story.
One you don't like
telling people.
People I trust.
My paramour Ellaria, she would
find you very interesting.
You should come to
the brothel and meet her.
We brought our own wine, not
the swill they serve here.
We have some lovely
boys on retainer, but...
You did like boys before?
Really?
Girls? Hmm.
I hope you won't be offended when
I say I never would have guessed.
Not at all.
But I was never interested
in girls, either.
- What then?
-  Nothing.
Everybody is interested
in something.
Not me.
When I see what
desire does to people,
what it's done to this country,
I am very glad
to have no part in it.
Besides, the absence of desire
leaves one free to pursue
other things.
Such as?
Let me guess,
I've been pardoned.
Really?
Father's orders.
Well, we mustn't
disappoint Father.
Kingslayer!
I, Tommen
of the House Baratheon,
First of my Name,
King of the Andals
and the First Men,
and Lord of the Seven Kingdoms,
do hereby recuse myself
from this trial.
Tywin of the House Lannister,
Hand of the King,
Protector of the Realm,
will sit as judge in my stead.
And with him Prince Oberyn
of the House Martell
and Lord Mace
of the House Tyrell.
And if found guilty...
may the gods punish the accused.
Tyrion of the House Lannister,
you stand accused by
the Queen Regent of regicide.
Did you kill King Joffrey?
No.
Did your wife, the Lady Sansa?
Not that I know of.
How would you say he died, then?
Choked on his pigeon pie.
So you would blame the bakers?
Or the pigeons.
Just leave me out of it.
The crown may call
its first witness.
Once we'd got
King Joffrey safely away
from the mob,
the Imp rounded on him.
He slapped the king
across the face
and called him a vicious
idiot and a fool.
It wasn't the first time
the Imp threatened Joffrey.
Right here in this throne room,
he marched up those steps
and called our king a halfwit.
Compared His Grace
to the Mad King
and suggested he'd meet
the same fate.
And when I spoke
in the king's defense,
he threatened to have me killed.
Oh, why don't you tell
them what Joffrey was doing?
- Silence.
- Pointing a loaded crossbow at Sansa Stark
while you tore at her
clothes and beat her.
Silence!
You will not speak
unless called upon.
You're dismissed, Ser Meryn.
Basilisk venom,
widow's blood,
wolfsbane,
essence of nightshade,
sweetsleep,
tears of Lys,
demon's dance...
blind eye...
I think you have made your
point, Grand Maester.
You have a lot of poison
in your store.
Had, Prince Oberyn.
My stores were plundered.
By whom?
By the accused,
Tyrion Lannister,
after he had me
wrongfully imprisoned.
Grand Maester,
you examined
King Joffrey's corpse.
Was it without question
poison that killed him?
Without question.
This was found on the body
of Dontos Hollard,
the king's fool.
He was last seen
spiriting Sansa Stark,
the wife of the accused,
away from the feast.
She wore this necklace
the day of the wedding.
Residue of a most rare
and terrible poison
was found inside.
Was this one of the poisons
stolen from your store?
It was.
The Strangler.
A poison few in
the Seven Kingdoms possess.
And used to strike down
the most noble child
the gods ever put
on this good earth.
"I will hurt you for this.
A day will come when you
think you are safe and happy
and your joy will turn
to ashes in your mouth
and you will know
the debt is paid."
Your own brother
said this to you?
Shortly before the Battle
of Blackwater Bay.
I confronted him about his plans
to put Joffrey on the front lines.
As it turned out,
when the attack came,
Joff insisted on remaining
at the battlements.
He believed his presence
would inspire the troops.
Tyrion said,
"And you will know
the debt is paid."
What debt?
I discovered
he'd been keeping whores
in the Tower of the Hand.
I asked him to confine
his salacious acts
to the brothel
where such behavior belongs.
He wasn't pleased.
Thank you, Your Grace,
for the courage
of your testimony.
Do you remember the
precise nature of this threat?
I'm afraid I do, my lord.
He said, "Perhaps you should
speak more softly to me, then.
Monsters are dangerous
and just now kings
are dying like flies."
And he said this to you at a
meeting of the small council?
Yes.
After we received word
of Robb Stark's death.
He didn't seem gladdened
by the news.
Perhaps his marriage
to Sansa Stark
had made him more sympathetic
to the northern cause.
You're excused, Lord Varys.
Father, may I ask
the witness one question?
One.
You once said
that without me, this city would
have faced certain defeat.
You said the histories
would never mention me,
but you would not forget.
Have you forgotten, Lord Varys?
Sadly, my lord,
I never forget a thing.
We will adjourn for now.
Toll the bells
in an hour's time.
Clear the court!
You'd condemn
your own son to death?
I've condemned no one.
The trial is not over.
This isn't a trial.
It's a farce.
Cersei has manipulated
everything and you know it.
I know nothing of the sort.
- You've always hated Tyrion.
- He killed his king.
As did I.
Do you know the last order
the Mad King gave me?
To bring him your head.
I saved your life so you
could murder my brother?
- It won't be murder. It'll be justice.
- Justice?
I'm performing my sworn
duty as Hand of the King.
If Tyrion is found guilty, he
will be punished accordingly.
- He'll be executed.
- No, he'll be punished accordingly.
Once you said family
is what lives on.
All that lives on.
You told me about a dynasty
that would last 1,000 years.
What happens to your dynasty
when Tyrion dies?
I'm a Kingsguard,
forbidden by oath
to carry on the family line.
I'm well aware of your oath.
What happens to your name?
Who carries the lion banner
into future battles?
Your nephews?
Lancel Lannister?
Others whose names
I don't even remember?
What happens to my dynasty
if I spare the life
of my grandson's killer?
It survives through me.
I'll leave the Kingsguard.
I'll take my place
as your son and heir
if you let Tyrion live.
Done.
When the testimony's concluded
and a guilty verdict rendered,
Tyrion will be given
the chance to speak.
He'll plead for mercy. I'll allow
him to join the Night's Watch.
In three days' time, he'll
depart for Castle Black
and live out his days
at the Wall.
You'll remove your
white cloak immediately.
You will leave King's Landing
to assume your rightful
place at Casterly Rock.
You will marry a suitable woman
and father children
named Lannister.
And you'll never turn your
back on your family again.
You have my word.
And you have mine.
Not going well, is it?
- You're going to be found guilty.
- Oh, you think so?
When you are, you need to
enter a formal plea for mercy
and ask to be sent to the Wall.
Father's agreed to it.
He'll spare your life and allow
you to join the Night's Watch.
Ned Stark was promised
the same thing
and we both know
how that turned out.
Father is not Joffrey.
He'll keep his word.
How do you know?
Do you trust me?
Keep your mouth shut.
No more outbursts.
This will all be over soon.
The crown may call
its next witness.
State your name.
Shae.
Do you swear by all the gods
that your testimony
will be true and honest?
I swear it.
Do you know this man?
Yes.
Tyrion Lannister.
How do you know him?
I was handmaiden
to his wife Lady Sansa.
This man stands accused
of murdering King Joffrey.
What do you know of this?
I know that he's guilty.
He and Sansa
planned it together.
Silence!
Continue.
She wanted revenge
for her father,
her mother, her brother.
She blamed their deaths
on the king.
Tyrion was happy to help.
He hated Joffrey.
He hated the queen.
He hated you, my lord.
He stole poison from
the Grand Maester's chamber
to put in Joffrey's wine.
How could you
possibly know all this?
Why would he reveal
such plans to his wife's maid?
I wasn't just her maid.
I was his whore.
I beg your pardon?
You said you were his...
His whore.
How did you come
to be in his service?
He stole me.
I was with another man,
a knight in
your lordship's army.
But when Tyrion arrived
at the camp,
he sent one of his cutthroats
into our tent.
He broke the knight's arm
and brought me to Lord Tyrion.
"You belong to me now," he said.
"I want you to fuck me like it's
my last night in this world."
Silence.
Silence!
And did you?
Did I what?
Fuck him like it was
his last night in this world.
I did everything he wanted.
Whatever he told me
to do to him.
Whatever he felt like doing to me.
I kissed him where he wanted.
I licked him where he wanted.
I let him put himself
where he wanted.
I was his property.
I would wait in his chambers
for hours
so he could use me
when he was bored.
He ordered me to call
him "my lion," so I did.
I took his face
in my hands and said,
"I am yours
and you are mine."
Shae.
Please don't.
I am a whore.
Remember?
That was before
he married Sansa.
After that,
all he wanted was her.
But she wouldn't let him
into her bed.
So he promised to kill
King Joffrey for her.
I wish to confess.
I wish...
to confess.
You wish to confess?
I saved you.
I saved this city
and all your worthless lives.
I should have let
Stannis kill you all.
Tyrion.
Do you wish to confess?
Yes, Father.
I'm guilty.
Guilty. Is that what
you want to hear?
You admit you poisoned the king?
No, of that I'm innocent.
I'm guilty of a far
more monstrous crime.
I am guilty of being a dwarf.
You are not on trial
for being a dwarf.
Oh, yes, I am.
I've been on trial
for that my entire life.
Have you nothing to say
in your defense?
Nothing but this...
I did not do it.
I did not kill Joffrey,
but I wish that I had.
Watching your vicious
bastard die
gave me more relief
than 1,000 lying whores.
I wish I was the monster
you think I am.
I wish I had enough poison
for the whole pack of you.
I would gladly give my life
to watch you all swallow it.
Ser Meryn. Ser Meryn.
Escort the prisoner
back to his cell.
I will not give my life
for Joffrey's murder.
And I know I'll get
no justice here.
So I will let
the gods decide my fate.
I demand a trial by combat.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com